<custom-action actionType="RTEConnect" isHit="true" name="connect" uid="a7632392-9966-4a10-9dfc-6a3bb7c4d46f">
    <description>Connect to a terminal server

Possible parameters are:
- Transport layer (required): Transport layer to use.
- Port (required): Port number to connect to. Default value is "23".
- Hostname (required): Hostname or IP address of the remote terminal.
- Use extended (optional): Use extended mode.
- Model (required): Model of the terminal.
- Timeout (ms) (required): Timeout. Default value is "1000".
- Terminal family (required): Terminal family.
- Wait (optional): Specify what to wait for in the terminal to be ready to receive the next action. Possible syntaxes are: 
	- CursorPosition(1x2) to wait until the cursor is at the first column and second row 
	- CursorPosition(1x2 after: "text") to wait until the cursor is at the first column, second row and after the pattern 'text' 
	- CursorPosition(1x2 after: "text", onWritableField) to wait until the cursor is at the first column, second row, after the pattern 'text' and on a 
	writable field (only applicable to TN3270 terminal) 
	- Text("text") to wait until the pattern 'text' is present on the screen 
	- Text(1x2 "text") to wait until the pattern 'text' is present on the screen at the first column and second line 
	- Text(1x2 3x4 "text") to wait until the pattern 'text' is present on the screen between the first column second line and the third column forth line 
	- RegExp("Hello.*") to wait until the regular expression 'Hello.*' have a match on the screen 
	- RegExp(1x2 "Hello.*") to wait until the regular expression 'Hello.*' have a match on the screen at the first column and second row 
	- CursorVisible to wait until the cursor is visible 
	- CursorHidden to wait until the cursor is hidden 
	- KeyboardLocked to wait until the keyboard is locked 
	- KeyboardUnlocked to wait until the keyboard is unlocked 
	- Connected to wait until the terminal is connected 
	- Disconnected to wait until the terminal is disconnected 
	- ScreenRefresh to wait until the first screen refresh 
	- Time(1000) to wait for 1000 milliseconds.
- WaitTimeout (optional): Timeout to wait for in milliseconds, based on the Wait parameter. Default value is "10000".
- Charset (optional): Charset to use.
- Username (optional): Username to use for the connection.
- Password (optional): Password to use for the connection.
- Private Key (optional): Private key used for the connection.
</description>
    <custom-action-parameter name="Transport layer" type="TEXT" value=""/>
    <custom-action-parameter name="Port" type="TEXT" value="23"/>
    <custom-action-parameter name="Hostname" type="TEXT" value=""/>
    <custom-action-parameter name="Use extended" type="TEXT" value=""/>
    <custom-action-parameter name="Model" type="TEXT" value=""/>
    <custom-action-parameter name="Timeout (ms)" type="TEXT" value="1000"/>
    <custom-action-parameter name="Terminal family" type="TEXT" value=""/>
    <custom-action-parameter name="Wait" type="TEXT" value=""/>
    <custom-action-parameter name="WaitTimeout" type="TEXT" value="10000"/>
    <custom-action-parameter name="Charset" type="TEXT" value=""/>
    <custom-action-parameter name="Username" type="TEXT" value=""/>
    <encrypted-custom-action-parameter name="Password" type="PASSWORD" value="W08qirDOdrMIl9FRe3jPX5Bnx9c/uURUa5X/C94/3fd2I3ZMJh0S8kstubxaWrh5$3"/>
    <custom-action-parameter name="Private Key" type="TEXT" value=""/>
</custom-action>
